<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-09-02T16:08:06-05:00</updated><id>https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Penny University</title><subtitle>A colection of ideas where the only realation is the url</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Fastai Chapter 1</title><link href="https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/markdown/2021/09/05/fastai-chp-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fastai Chapter 1" /><published>2021-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/markdown/2021/09/05/fastai-chp-1</id><author><name></name></author><category term="markdown" /><summary type="html">TLDR; And so it begins What is this about A couple of years ago myself and the youtube algorithm sat down and decided that it would be a good idea if I watched the fastai course. Needless to say this turned out to be a very good decision. Now, getting things sorted for masters applications and worn down by Jeremy’s near constant reminders about the virtue of blogging, I’m going to write a few things about the fastai course. Partly, because I think I might fun (I have been told by normal people that I might be using this word incorrectly) and I’ve just got some ADHD medication and now suddenly have all this time in the day to contribute to the 3rd best type of evidence. Typo: Top should read “Confirms my epistemic priors” What this is The parts of the chapter I found to be interesting - my background is the sort of where I have to ask the poor innocent person who was just making conversation how much time do they have to hear a story far longer than they were expecting. A broader look at the topic - the book does a good job of providing a lot of context, but I do have a History A-level and I’m not afraid to use it What this isn’t A in depth study guide of the course. These already exist, not to say there won’t be tutorial-esq things, just that focus will be general interest. Conclusion Hope you will join on this little yomp with fastai, this might be copyright infringement on Zach Mueller’s Walk with Fastai, but until lawyers come knocking we’ll go with that. But if you like your educational content slightly sequitous and irreverently loquacious, then maybe stick around.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fastai Chapter Blog Series</title><link href="https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/markdown/2021/09/03/fastai-chp-0.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fastai Chapter Blog Series" /><published>2021-09-03T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-09-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/markdown/2021/09/03/fastai-chp-0</id><author><name></name></author><category term="markdown" /><summary type="html">TLDR; It’s a ramblely blog series around the fastai course (V4/fastbook) Read if: you want fun tangents about stuff Don’t read if: you want a focused course summary What is this about A couple of years ago myself and the youtube algorithm sat down and decided that it would be a good idea if I watched the fastai course. Needless to say this turned out to be a very good decision. Now, getting things sorted for masters applications and worn down by Jeremy’s near constant reminders about the virtue of blogging, I’m going to write a few things about the fastai course. Partly, because I think I might fun (I have been told by normal people that I might be using this word incorrectly) and I’ve just got some ADHD medication and now suddenly have all this time in the day to contribute to the 3rd best type of evidence. Typo: Top should read “Confirms my epistemic priors” What this is The parts of the chapter I found to be interesting - my background is the sort of where I have to ask the poor innocent person who was just making conversation how much time do they have to hear a story far longer than they were expecting. A broader look at the topic - the book does a good job of providing a lot of context, but I do have a History A-level and I’m not afraid to use it. What this isn’t An in depth study guide of the course. These already exist, not to say there won’t be tutorial-esq things, just that focus will be general interest. Conclusion Hope you will join on this little yomp with fastai, this might be copyright infringement on Zach Mueller’s Walk with Fastai, but until lawyers come knocking we’ll go with that. But if you like your educational content slightly sequitous and irreverently loquacious, then maybe stick around.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">An Example Markdown Post</title><link href="https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/markdown/2020/08/27/test-markdown-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="An Example Markdown Post" /><published>2020-08-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/markdown/2020/08/27/test-markdown-post</id><author><name></name></author><category term="markdown" /><summary type="html">Example Markdown Post</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fastpages Notebook Blog Post</title><link href="https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/jupyter/2020/02/20/test.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fastpages Notebook Blog Post" /><published>2020-02-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-02-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/jupyter/2020/02/20/test</id><author><name></name></author><category term="jupyter" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/images/chart-preview.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://lukemshepherd.github.io/penny-university/images/chart-preview.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>